In 1999, the Akihabara Maid Cafe
industry was led by two major players,
the Creatureland and Maid Alien groups.
The two forces were in a delicate balance.
Despite minor scuffles
among low-ranking cafes,
the town maintained a facade of peace.
But then,
Ronko Maanen returns to being a maid
after serving 15 years for a gang war.
On her very first day, Ronko annihilates
a maid cafe from a rival group.
She raids a casino,
an underground fight club, and even a cafe
affiliated with her same parent group.
As tensions rise, the one behind
made aliens rise to prominence.
A maid known as Crimson
Supernova returns to Akihabara.
It's an honor to have you back.
Thank you.
Gotta feel the winds of
freedom, you know what I mean?
Thank you so much for joining us.
Hey, I'm made of way
It's good to have you back, Manami.
And who the hell are you?
I'm the current head, Ugaki.
From this day forward, you work for me.
What's happening with Akiba Big Bang?
It's coming along just fine, of course.
Ever since I became head,
we've doubled our earnings and
we're gaining fast on Creature Land.
Why is it I see no one
from Wuv Wuv Moonbeam here?
They're no longer among us.
What the hell does that mean?
They misbehaved a tad too much and got
crushed by some Creature Underlings.
It was a shame, really.
Anyway, Manami, put that
thing down and let's eat.
Flinging around guns, blades,
and bats is a thing of the past.
So what were you all
doing the seven years I
was sitting behind bars
eating prison sloth?
Listen here.
I'm the second generation head.
You're just one of the senior members.
Remember your place.
Don't you see having
these softies around makes
made alien look like a
bunch of damn wusses?
Those days are over.
What's that?
You don't care that
they talk shit about us?
And you call yourself a fucking maid?
It's important for a
maid to have credibility.
Please calm down, Manami. Tell me, Chief.
Aren't you angry not settling
a scoring at how we maids do?
Yes, of course, of course, you're right.
Then why don't you tell me
what's been happening and
which creature bastards
took out Wub Wub Moonbeam?
Oinky-doink, oink.
Oinky-doink cafe, Miss Manami.
the oinky-doink
Manami
So the Crimson Supernova is back
First of all,
wiping out a sister cafe and a
lucrative one like Maid Sheep is
inexcusable behavior But they were
the ones who started Second of all,
Maid Alien has lodged a complaint with
us about how you crushed Wub Wub Moonbeam
After all this time?
That doesn't change the
fact that you did it.
But that wasn't really our fault.
Do you think pigs are really
creatures to begin with?
Oh, please let us still be creatures!
You can only be called creatures
when you can contribute to the group.
Uh...
This matter of you
crushing Wav Wav Moonbeam.
Go settle it with Made Alien.
We're done here.
But, um, a tiny cafe like us can't do
anything about a major group like...
Then if you can't, pigs will
become extinct here in Akiba.
Welcome.
Beer, please.
Plus soy sauce ramen and
a pork cutlet rice bowl.
We look like we're in the same business.
Well, yes, I... No, no need.
I'm just here for the chow today.
Nothing better than some ramen and beer.
Make it two glasses, please.
Never thought a joint like
this would still be around.
Young ones these days just don't get it.
This is the stuff, yo.
The fact that this ramen shop is
here is enough to keep Hanakiba.
Very well said, lady.
I appreciate it.
New ain't always the answer to everything.
Some things best not change or be changed.
You know what I mean, lady?
Ubi.
What is that?
So yeah, they're totally
done for. You sure? Mm-hmm.
Uh...
What's going on around here?
Everyone's on edge right now.
It's kind of strange,
but our group has changed its policies
now that Crimson Supernova is back.
Who?
They're saying we need
to wipe out anything
that stands in the way
of the Akiva Big Bang.
And that we might have to
go to war with Creatureland.
Seriously?
But I was hoping to be better
friends with you, Nerula.
Nagomi!
I need everyone at the Oinky Doink.
Oh, a friend of yours? Yes, Chief.
This is Nerula from Invader Cafe Destron.
It's very nice to meet you, madam.
Um, I'm the manager at Oinkidoink. Nice
to meet you. It's a pleasure. Okay, great.
Nagomi, let's go.
Oh, uh, okay. See ya. Bye.
So there you have it.
It's now our job to do
something about Maid Alien.
What do you mean by something?
To put it bluntly, it means
we're supposed to go die.
So you mean Creature Land's
just gonna abandon us?
Are you kidding me?
Let's take the five million
from the sheep and the run.
You really think there's
anywhere we can run to?
Then how about we take it back
to Made Alien and say sorry?
Like five million's even enough.
Made Alien is a major player on
par with the Creatureland group.
Then we'll have to take out their leader.
An assassination.
That sounds practical.
The head of the group?
Won't you be heavily guarded by aliens?
I mean, like, who's even the
head of Made Alien anyway?
The Crimson Supernova.
Crimson what?
Apparently they're back with Made Alien.
Maybe if we apologize really
hard they'll forgive us you
should have realized by now
that that kind of thinking
won't fly in this business
yeah I know that but it's just
yeah yeah I know you still
don't like the whole violence
aspect but hey someone might
die trying to protect you if
you can't fight hear me yes
that's right I'd like to get
some information on the head
of made alien uh no wait hold
on please uh hello she seriously
just hung up on me damn it
Huh hey what's up nagomi do you think
we're going to have to fight made alien
it's just i really don't want to have to
fight my friend have to fight a friend oh
you mean sure i get it of course you don't
want to fight her i don't know what to do
What if you become sisters?
Sisters?
How do we become sisters?
Oh, it's easy.
You just swear an oath with another
maid and exchange name tags.
But Nerula is a member
of the Maid Alien group.
Yes, of course.
You can't hope for our leader's blessing.
That's not even a possibility.
But you understand that the bond of sisterhood
is super important to a maid, right?
There's a bond of sisterhood?
Here in this cafe, I'm known
as your parent, Nogomi.
I'd be happy to act as a witness.
Do you think Nerula will
agree to being my sister?
Sure she will!
She's your friend, isn't she?
Nagomi?
Making an oath of sisterhood, I worried may
be risky with a maid from another group.
Speaking from experience, taking an oath
of sisterhood isn't a definite thing.
You had a bonded sister, Ronko?
Yes, a long time ago.
She was a fellow maid
at the cafe I worked at.
She was very capable at her duties.
I thought we were sisters, Ronka.
Why are you so against this?
You know that Miss Michio decided
on a non-aggressive defense policy.
Going out on the offense
would go against her wishes.
Protecting this cafe
serves to protect her.
For that, we've got to fight.
I disagree.
I have no idea where she is now.
Are you against this sisterhood?
Oinky Dwing Cafe is now at
odds with the made alien group.
We can't rule out the possibility of
Nerula turning on you at some point.
Even knowing that, I still
want to stick by Nerula's side.
Nagomi!
What's going on?
Well, um, you see,
I, um, I want you to join me in an oath
of sisterhood and be friends forever!
Huh? Please!
But, Nagomi, we can't.
You and I belong to different groups.
They won't allow it.
I know that! Still!
You're being serious?
This is my show of resolve.
I want to become sisters with
you and stay friends forever.
Well, I guess I'm going
to be a big sister.
I'll do it.
Let's be sisters, Nagomi.
I'm so happy.
I thought you might say
no and think I'm crazy.
No matter what the higher-ups might
say, I'm going to dream big and go, go.
Let us partake.
We have partaken.
Congratulations.
As you two are now bonded in sisterhood,
may it be everlasting and joyous.
Now please ready your hands.
Yo!
Don't let your noodles get limp. Right.
Wow, Pops.
You're used to conducting
these things, huh?
Been a long time.
You can have the pork, Nagomi.
Then you take the egg, Nerula.
Let's go crush that pigsty
they call the oinky-doink.
Rampage and plunder to
your heart's content.
What's with the pouty faces?
If you want to say something, spit it out.
A lot of things have changed
since you've been gone.
Why do we have to do things different?
The creatures in us, we've
kept a respectful distance.
Y 'all are mighty cocky when it comes
to sitting there bitching and moaning.
So what is it then?
You think the kind of sissy
ETs who stand by and let wuv
wuv moonbeam get crushed can
make the Akiba Big Bang happen?
I mean, what's this Akiba Big Bang anyway?
That is the Akiba Big Bang!
How could you be a part of
Made Alien and not know that?
Listen up.
Made Alien maids are extra
Akiba terrestrial invaders.
All wussy maids get sunk
in the sea of tranquility!
You hear me?
If y 'all can't exterminate
those filthy swine,
then it'll be your cafes that
will all get a nice, good probing.
Hmm.
Now that you've made an oath of
sisterhood, she's your sister, right?
That means she's basically like
a daughter to me, you know?
Let's have her over sometime for a visit.
Wouldn't that be too dangerous right now?
Just a casual mother and daughter thing.
I'd love to have a nice long chat with
her, like about Nerula's little cafe,
and about Maid Alien, and...
Chief, exploiting a bond of sisterhood?
You've got to be kidding.
But we really don't have
a choice now, do we?
I don't really get what's
going on right now.
She wants a spy.
I'd really love to get some info on
the head of Maid Alien and stuff.
Because, hey, us and Maid Alien,
we're like sardines up against a
sperm whale, so getting info is key.
You're despicable.
What kind of person does that?
Don't you realize we're all gonna
get slaughtered at this rate?
I'm like an overprotective
parent to you, remember?
Come on, show your adorn mommy some love.
True that, it may be our
only viable prospect.
Yeah, given the situation.
A spy is our only hope.
Please, I'm begging you.
That's not gonna happen.
This is a test of your dignity as a maid.
Every one of you maids must do what
you should as members of Maid Alien.
Wubwub Moonbeam was viciously
ravaged by the creatures.
Time to kill the guilty pigs.
We will prove our superior
prowess to the universe and use
this opportunity to exterminate
all creatures from Akiba.
The war for our world is imminent.
Hello, Mistress.
We have a starfruit event
going on this month.
Ooh, that's yummy.
We're having a top shot pork
chop dance that sounds lovely.
Um. Hey.
Do you want to come visit?
Our cafe. Oh.
Are you okay? So. Sorry.
I'm fine.
Here.
Uh. Yeah. Right.
Thanks for helping me pick them up.
You mean for real, they're
actually after us now?
So they're planning to crush us
to trigger an all-out war, huh?
This is valuable info.
If not for this note, we
would have been sitting ducks.
Totally awesome.
This is great.
We should thank the spy. Nagomi!
Thank you, dutiful daughter!
I didn't do anything!
Oh, okay. Never mind then.
Let's get ready.
Miss Manami, the cops are here. Huh?
I heard you got a new acting head, so I
figured I should drop by and say hello.
Oh, by the way, I hear you're going to have
a romp with Creatureland sometime soon.
I don't think I know what
you mean by all that.
Well, we got tipped off, you see.
It's just we police have
to investigate these
things or we meet the
wrath of the citizens.
But it really looks like made aliens
doing rather well, aren't they?
Officer,
I just came back to
town and can't tell the
Shower Dory exit from
the Electric Town exit.
I do hope we can rely on you for guidance.
That's good money down the drain
where'd that leak come from?
Go find that goddamn squealing rat!
Right by the way, apparently the police
rep made alien headquarters the other day?
So wait does Does that
mean we're safe to stroll?
We cannot let our guard down.
We should be on high alert for a while.
So make sure you don't go anywhere alone.
I haven't been able to reach Nerula since
she handed me that note the other day.
I'm sure she's fine.
She's a tough kid, so don't worry.
I can tell that about people.
Nagomi, do you wish to go
out and search for Nerula?
I want to do what I can for her.
Then I shall accompany you on
your strolls starting tomorrow.
Huh?
The oinky-doink is being
targeted right now,
so we need to make sure
we are on our guard.
Thank you.
Pretty certain this is the one.
Gotta erase her then.
We're tracking her down now.
No sign of Nerula on
the street today either.
Have you been able to sleep at all lately?
No, I'm too worried.
She's alive. What?
I said the kid's alive.
Have you seen Nerula recently?
Yeah.
Well, tell us!
Where was she?
Nerula!
Why are you here, Nogomi?
I'm so glad you're okay.
I'm so sorry I caused you to worry.
They're looking for me
because I betrayed Maid Alien.
Because of me?
No.
Because I wanted to.
I'm glad I got to see you
one last time, Nogomi.
One last time?
I'm going to stick by
my own Maid principles.
What do we have here?
What are you doing?
Conspiring with the swine?
Just making small talk.
You know what you've gone and done,
getting in the way of us crushing the pigs?
That traitorous mouth of yours
needs permanent shutting.
And I would do it again.
No, Gomi.
We should go now.
What do you mean, do it again?
This is between me and the made aliens.
You two should leave.
You're the quiet one I met
at the old ramen joint.
That's too bad.
And here I thought we
were gonna be friends.
Yeah, it's a shame, isn't it?
I suppose it was meant to be, though.
I'll crush your face along with
the rest of you creature land pigs.
Why you you sure are brave you know
who you're pointing that blade at?
Yeah crimson supernova prepare to die!
Oh look at you trying to be
bad this better be worth it?
Miyabi, stay out of this!
Better loosen that grip there, brave one.
Nerula! Stay back!
Time to die.
Now you're just starting to annoy me.
Bronco, you've got to go help her!
This is their issue.
But if we don't do
anything, Nerula will...
That's what it means to be an Akiba maid.
Nerula knew just what she
was getting herself into.
Who cares about all that maid crap?
Nerula is my sister!
Those words are all I ever needed to hear.
Traitors only have one place to
go, and that's straight to hell.
No!
No! No!
No! No! No! No! No!
No!
No way! Please, no!
Harming one of ours goes
against the code, does it not?
Put that thing down.
All you do is cry without doing
shit, and you call yourself a maid?
Miss Minami, the cops are on their way.
Sounds like we're done here.
Now don't forget, pigs, our
war is just getting started.
What do I do?
The blood won't stop!
Let go of me.
I'm so sorry I dragged you into this.
No, no, you're wrong!
It was me!
I wish I could have lived
a little bit longer.
Sister, sister,
you won't ever change
the way you truly are.
Be the maid you are now.
No!
Thank you.
Ah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
Thank you so much for joining us today.